In a few minutes, the opening ceremony for Daihaseisai will begin!
（ｽﾋﾟｰｶｰ:ﾘﾎﾟｰﾀｰ）
あと数分で
大覇星(だいはせい)祭の開会式が始まります
Here, at Academy City, the streets are bustling about with the parents and siblings of our students!
ここ学園都市は どこも学生たちの
父兄や見学者で いっぱいです
Maid bentos here!
（舞夏(まいか)）
あ～ メイド弁当～
Would you like Academy City's famous maid bentos?
学園都市名物 メイド弁当は
要らんかね？
Ryouran Kasei Girl's School maid's—
or rather, maid-in-training bentos?
繚乱(りょうらん)家政女学校のメイド弁当
より正確には
メイド見習い弁当は要らんかね？
Oh my, there are a lot of schools in Academy City.
（詩菜(しいな)）
あらあら　学園都市って
いろいろな学校があるのね
Y-Yeah.
It's a city where all the world's top educational institutions are concentrated into one place.
世界中のあらゆる教育機関を
凝縮させたような場所だからね
S-Sorry.
（ぶつかる音）
あっ す… すいません
（美鈴(みすず)）
あっ こちらこそ ごめんなさい
I'm sorry, that was my fault.
Would you happen to know where Tokiwadai Middle School is?
あの… 常盤台(ときわだい)中学って
どの辺にあるかご存じですか？
あっ ちょっと待ってください
Just a moment...
Tokiwadai... Tokiwadai...
常盤台 常盤台…
It's not here. Maybe it isn't open to the public?
ないなぁ　もしかして
一般公開されていないのでは？
What, seriously?
（美鈴）
えっ？　ホントですか？
Then where on Earth is Mikoto?
じゃ 美琴(みこと)のヤツは どこにいるのよ
Is this Mikoto-san a sister of yours?
そ… その美琴さんというのは
妹さんか何かで？
Oh my, Touya-san...
刀夜さん　またですか？
Are you at it again?
It really isn't here! What should I do?
M-Mother... what do you mean "again?"
か… 母さん　またって…
Oh? Isn't that Touma-san over there?
（詩菜）
あら？
あれは当麻(とうま)さんじゃありません？
Fine then!
（上条(かみじょう)）
ああ いいぜ　もし
お前に負けるようなことがあったら
If I lose, I'll do a penalty game.
罰ゲーム食らってもいいし
何でも言うこと聞いてやるよ
I'll do anything you ask.
All right, you're on!
（美琴）
よ～し 乗った
何でもね？　何でも
Anything goes, right?
その代わり お前も負けたら
ちゃんと罰ゲームだからな
The same goes for you if you lose.
えっ？　そ… それって つまり…
何でも言うこと…
S-So, wait...
I have to do anything you—
What's that?
あれあれ？　たった今
ここで放った大口には―
Is that really all the confidence you have after running your mouth like that?
それくらいの自信しか
なかったのかな？
Fine, you're on.
いいわよ　やってやろうじゃない
I'm not letting you cry your way out of it later.
（美琴）
あとで
泣き見るんじゃないわよ あんた
Oh my...
フフッ… 美琴ちゃんも元気ね
Mikoto-chan looks happy.
～♪
#08 Daihaseisai
The Daihaseisai will begin soon, correct?
（ローラ）
そちらは そろそろ―
大覇星祭の
開会式でしょう？
Won't you be paying them a visit?
（ﾛｰﾗ）
挨拶のひとつも必要ではないかと
思うのだけど
Do you really think I can let people see me like this?
（ｱﾚｲｽﾀｰ）
私が この姿で
人前に出るとでも思うのか？
Then let's not hesitate to continue our conversation.
（ﾛｰﾗ）
なら 遠慮なしに話を進めましょう
（ｱﾚｲｽﾀｰ）
学園都市内部へ
侵入した魔術師のことか？
About the magicians who've infiltrated Academy City?
They're taking the chance while city security is relaxed.
甘くなりし警備の隙を突いてね
We've managed to confirm that there are two of them.
今のところ
こちらが確認せしは２名とのこと
A high ranking member of the Roman Catholic Church, and a courier she hired.
ローマ正教の重役と
彼女に雇われたる運び屋ね
Their objective is a particular object.
目的たるは とある物品の
取り引きといいたるところよ
A particular object?
（ｱﾚｲｽﾀｰ）
とある物品？
よっこいしょ…
A sword?
（ｱﾚｲｽﾀｰ）剣(つるぎ)か
（ﾛｰﾗ）これはレプリカだけど
This is just a replica.
"Stab Sword."
刺突杭剣(スタブソード)よ
They say it can slay a dragon and pin it to the ground.
竜をも貫き 地面に
縫い止めたる剣(つるぎ)とまでいわれたるの
If successfully handed over, the Church of England will be in a rather dreadful predicament.
渡る所へ渡れば―
我々イギリス清教は
一気に窮地に立たされんとするわ
A so-called "tactical weapon" for your side?
（ｱﾚｲｽﾀｰ）
そちらの世界の
戦術兵器といったところか
Here's the biggest issue:
最大の問題たるは
この刺突杭剣(スタブソード)の取り引きが―
The trade for the sword is happening within Academy City.
学園都市内部で
行われんとしていることね
Which means...
（ｱﾚｲｽﾀｰ）
…となると 旅のガイドとして―
We'll have to get that boy to be the travel guide.
あの少年を
起用するしかないわけだが
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
わあ！
Hey, Touma!
当麻 当麻　私 おなかすいたかも
I'm hungry!
えっ？　さっき
朝ご飯 食べたばかりじゃねえか
Huh?
You just ate breakfast.
でも そこかしこから
何とも言えない匂いが漂ってきて
But there's such a delicious smell everywhere that I can't stand it!
それどころじゃないんだよ
（猫の鳴き声）
ああ 日本の料理文化は
食という名の誘惑の塊かも
Japan's food culture is the essence of food temptation!
Okay, fine.
ああ 分かった 分かった
あとで一緒に回ってやるから
We can walk around later and check it out.
Later?
あとで？
ああ　もう最初の競技が始まるから
Yeah.
The first match is starting soon.
All the events I'm participating in today are marked in this.
（上条）
今日 俺が参加する種目
そこに印ついてっから
Let's go, Index!
行くぞ インデックス
T-Touma seems really dull today...
き… 今日の当麻は
なんだか ものすごくドライかも
（青髪ﾋﾟｱｽ）
アア… やる気な～い
Do we really have to...
Why does everyone look so weary before we've even started?
皆さん 初日から この
グッタリしたテンションは一体…
We used up what little energy we had fighting over what strategy to use to defeat the other schools.
（青髪ﾋﾟｱｽ）
こっちは どうやって
ほかの学校に勝つかをモメまくって
少ない体力をゼロにまで
すり減らしてしまいましたが 何か
Get your priorities straight!
本末転倒じゃねえか！
That's what student matches are.
（姫神(ひめがみ)）
学生の競技なんて 所詮 そんなもの
Such misfortune.
不幸だ…
What's with this lack of spirit?
（吹寄(ふきよせ)）何なの？　この無気力感は
（上条）うん？
Hey, Kamijou!
（吹寄）
まさか 上条
貴様が むやみに だらけるから
それが みんなに伝染して…
Don't tell me you infected everyone else with your laziness!
I only just got here!
俺だって
今 やって来たとこなんだって
So everyone basically lost their motivation because you showed up late.
つまり 貴様が遅刻したから―
みんなのやる気が
なくなったということね？
（上条）
吹寄だって
俺より遅れてきたじゃん
You were later than I was, Fukiyose!
I had committee duties to take care of, idiot!
私は運営委員の仕事よ　バカ
Leave me alone!
もう放っておいてくれ
不幸な現実に直面した上条さんは
今ちょっと立ち上がれない状態なの
Kamijou-san has gotten himself into an unfortunate situation and he can't get up for the time being!
That's just anemia getting to you.
それは軽い貧血状態よ
Here, this sports drink will fix that.
ほら スポーツドリンクで補給しろ
I hate people who blame bad luck or fate for their own lack of resolve.
私はね
不幸とか不運とかを理由につけて
人生に手を抜く輩(やから)が大嫌いなの
Everyone's lost their motivation because of your laziness, so you'd better get it together!
貴様１人が だらけると
周りのやる気もなくなる
だから
シャキッとしなさい シャキッと
U-Um...
あ… あの…
U-Uh...
そ… その…
Is there a problem?
（吹寄）何か文句が？
（上条）えっ？
None whatsoever, Ma'am!
あ… ありませんです！　はい！
ハァ… 誰も
棒倒しどころじゃなくなってやがる
Nobody even wants to play Pole Assault anymore.
もうホントにダメかも
This may seriously be hopeless...
（小萌(こもえ)）
だから ウチの設備に
不備があるのは認めるのです
Like I said, I realize that our equipment and curriculum are lacking!
But that isn't the fault of the students!
でも それは
生徒たちには何の非もないのですよ
（教師）
生徒の質が低いから―
Isn't it because their results are so low that the administrative board refuses to raise funding?
統括理事会から
追加資金が下りないのでしょう？
フッ… 失敗作を抱え込むと
いろいろ苦労しますね
You must have it pretty rough, teaching a bunch of failures like that.
（小萌）
ンンッ… せ… 生徒さんには
成功も失敗もないのです
S-Students can't simply be labeled as successes or failures!
They just have their own personalities.
あるのは
それぞれの個性だけなのですよ
（教師）
なかなか夢のあるご意見ですが
That's a pretty idealistic opinion.
これから始まる棒倒し
おたくの落ちこぼれたちを―
The Pole Assault that's starting now...
We'll be sure to completely crush those hopeless failures at your school.
完膚なきまでに
撃破してさし上げますよ
You're wrong...
違いますよね？
Our students aren't hopeless...
みんなは 落ちこぼれなんかじゃ
ありませんよね？
Hey, guys...
おい みんな　もう一度だけ聞く
Let me ask again.
Are we going to do this or not?
本当に やる気がねえのか？
First match: Pole Assault.
（ｱﾅｳﾝｽ）
第１種目 棒倒し　各校の入場です
The various school teams are entering.
What a reckless guy.
（美琴）
あいつも無謀よね
ウチの学校に勝てるわけもないのに
There's no way they can beat our school.
So hungry...
おなか減った
うん？　まさか
熱中症とかじゃないでしょうね？
Could she be suffering from heatstroke?
ハァ～ッ…
Oh, so you really are hungry.
あんた ホントに
おなかが減ってるだけなのね
What's Miss Short-Hair doing here?
短髪は ここで何してるの？
当麻の応援？
Cheering for Touma?
（美琴）
えっ？　なんで私が―
Wh-Why would I cheer for that guy?!
あんなヤツの応援なんか
しなくちゃならないわけ？
I just came to see which school will win.
大体 どっちの学校が勝つか
賭けしてんのよ
どうせ私が勝つに決まってんだから
Though it's obvious my school will.
Huh?
あれ？
勝っちゃったら どうしよう
What should I do then?
（美琴）何でも言うこと聞くって…
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）あっ 当麻だ！
He said he'd do anything I asked...
There's Touma!
Why does he look so determined?
一体 何なのよ　あの覚悟
ま… まさか
マジで勝ちに行く気なわけ？
Is he seriously going to try to win?
あいつ
私に勝って 何を要求する気なの？
What is he going to make me do once he wins?!
Get set...
（教師）用意… 始め！
（号砲）
Go!
ど… どうして みんな
Why did you all go so far just to win?
そんなになるまで
頑張っちゃうのですか？
Even though you won, seeing you all bruised like that makes me...
いくら勝っても―
そんなボロボロになっちゃった
みんなを見るのは…
先生は… 先生は…
Hey, Index!
（上条）
お～い　インデックス？
Man, she's so hopeless.
…たく しゃあねえな
Oh, my phone...
あっ 携帯… カバンか
I left it in my bag.
I-I came here to get my cellphone so I could contact someone I was separated from.
こ… これは迷子と合流するために
携帯電話を取ってこようと
やったことで―
I didn't have any bad intentions...
決して
よこしまな思いがあったわけでは…
（吹寄）フゥ…
（上条）えっ？
Huh?
あれ？
あっ いたいた！　当麻！
There you are, Touma!
Were you just crying?
あれ？　当麻 なんで涙目なの？
Where's your phone?
お前 携帯は？
Right here!
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）持ってるよ
（上条）じゃ なんで出ないんだよ
Then why didn't you answer?!
えっ？　バッテリー切れ…
Your battery's dead...
Nevermind that, I'm hungry!
そんなことより おなか減ったよ
何か食べさせてよ 当麻
Give me something to eat, Touma!
ハァ… 屋台エリアまで行きゃ
食べ物なんて山ほどあるだろう
If you go to the stands, there are mountains of food there.
山ほど！
Mountains!
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）えっ？
（黄泉川(よみかわ)）ああ　ごめんね
NO ENTRY
Oh, I'm sorry, there's a parade coming through here soon.
ここ
もうすぐパレードが始まるじゃんよ
（上条）
えっと…
あっちまで渡りたいんですけど
We only need to get over there...
西に３キロの地点にある地下街から
横断できるけど
There's a subway you can use to cross the street if you go about 3km west.
（上条）
３キロ…
3km...
But it's right there...
手を伸ばせば そこにあるのに
Well, we'll just have to wait until the Ball Rolling event is over.
次の大玉転がしが終わるまで我慢な
うん？
当麻…
Touma...
えっ？　なんで？
What?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）ンンッ！
（上条）ちょっと！
Wait!
あれ？
うっしゃー！
捕まえたわよ 私の勝利条件！
All right, I've got you! You're my ticket to victory!
The winner of the Borrowed Item Race is Misaka Mikoto of Tokiwadai Middle School!
（ｱﾅｳﾝｽ）
借り物競走 １位は
常盤台中学 御坂美琴選手です
借り物競走…
Borrowed Item Race?
（美琴）
そう
“第１種目で競技を行った高校生”
Yep. I had to find a high school student who participated in the first event.
And you just happen to fit the bill.
あんたでも
一応 当てはまるでしょう？
Aren't there a bunch of other people who'd fit—
そんな条件に合うヤツなんて
ほかにいくらでも…
な… 何すんだよ いきなり！
What the heck was that for?
もう… ほら これ飲みなさいよ…
Sheesh...
Here, drink this...
There's no other choice, so I'll let you have this!
しかたないから あげるわよ！
はい！
Well, you see, when I imagined you resting in bed while the rest of us were working in this blazing heat...
（初春(ういはる)）
いやぁ 私たちが
炎天下で頑張っている最中に―
白井(しらい)さんが
休養取ってる姿を想像すると
I just couldn't stop myself.
いても立っても
いられなくなっちゃって
I wanted you to help us out, too!
お仕事 手伝ってほしくなって
しまったんですよ フフッ…
（黒子(くろこ)）
フゥ… ステキすぎる友情を
ありがとうですわ
I thank you very much, my dear friend.
So, are there any problems?
…で
何か問題でも起きていますの？
（初春）
今のところは
Not at the moment.
（ｱﾅｳﾝｽ）
１位を獲得した御坂美琴選手は―
After taking first place, Misaka Mikoto remains in tip-top shape.
ゴール後も体勢を崩すことはなく
まだまだ余力を感じさせる姿を―
She continues to make everything look so easy.
見せてくれました
Onee-sama!
お姉様！
ああ 麗しきお姉様… えっ？
Oh, my beloved Onee-sama!
And here we see her taking care of her partner who ran with her.
（アナウンス）
一緒に走ってもらった
協力者さんを―
いたわる所も
好印象でした
I'll kill him!
殺す！
NO ENTRY
I can't find Index.
すっかり はぐれちまったけど
大丈夫か？　インデックス
Will she be okay?
It's him...
あいつは…
Academy City is most likely relaxing its security in order to attract a bigger audience.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
今の学園都市は―
一般来場客を招くために
警備を甘くしてるだろう
And magicians are taking this chance to infiltrate?
（土御門(つちみかど)）
その隙を突いて―
この中に魔術師たちが
侵入してるってわけだぜ
We've only confirmed two of them.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
現在 確認しているのは２人
Lidvia Lorenzetti of the Roman Catholic Church, and the courier she hired, Oriana Thompson.
ローマ正教の
リドヴィア＝ロレンツェッティ
そいつが雇った運び屋の
オリアナ＝トムソン
Courier?
（上条）運び屋？
（土御門）ヤツらは この町で―
They're making a trade with the Church's spiritual weapon here in this city.
教会に伝わる霊装の取り引きを
行おうとしている
なんで こんな所で…
Why here?
Isn't Academy City as far from the occult as you can get?
学園都市って オカルトから
いちばん縁のないとこだろう？
That's precisely why.
だからこそだにゃ
This is a place where neither the science side nor magic side can interfere easily.
学園都市側と魔術側 お互いに―
手を出しにくい場所なんだぜ
ここは
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
動けるのは 学園都市にやって来た
君の知り合いだけってことだ
In other words, the only people who can act are your buddies already in Academy City.
（上条）
じゃ 神裂(かんざき)は？
What about Kanzaki then?
あいつ 確か 聖人とかって…
Isn't she a Saint or something?
We can't use Kanzaki, especially not this time.
神裂は使えない　今回は特にね
Not with the spiritual weapon being what it is.
何しろ
取り引きされる霊装が霊装だ
えっ？　どういう意味だよ？
Huh?
What do you mean?
Kami-yan, the name of the weapon is "Stab Sword."
カミやん
その霊装の名前は刺突杭剣(スタブソード)
They say it can kill any Saint with a single strike.
あらゆる聖人を
一撃で即死させる物らしいんだ
Watch out!
（女子生徒）危ない！
（男子生徒）ヤバイ！
No!
Huh?
What?
えっ？　なんで？
ウワッ！
What are you doing, Kamijou Touma?!
何をやっているのよ 上条当麻！
Do you know how the Son of God was killed on the cross, Kami-yan?
（土御門）
十字架にかけられた神の子は―
一体 どうやって殺されたか
知ってるかい？　カミやん
Wasn't he... nailed there?
（上条）
確か 磔(はりつけ)にされて…
He was stabbed to death.
刺殺だよ
Stab Sword is a weapon that extracts the religious meaning of the nailing and stabbing,
（土御門）
刺突杭剣(スタブソード)ってのは―
処刑と刺殺の宗教的意味を抽出し
極限まで
増幅 凝縮 収束させた霊装ですたい
and amplifies, concentrates, and focuses it to its limit.
It would have no effect on normal humans, but it has a one-hit-kill ability if used against a Saint.
普通の人間には何の効果もないが
相手が聖人なら
一撃で葬る力を誇る
What do the magicians have planned, trading something like that?
そんな物(もん)を取り引きして―
魔術師たちは
何をするつもりなんだよ？
Preparing for war, of course.
（土御門）
もちろん 戦争だろうさ
聖人ってのは 魔術業界じゃ
核兵器に等しい意味を持つ
Saints have power equivalent to that of a nuclear weapon in the magical world.
But there are plenty of magicians who aren't Saints, right?
けど 聖人以外の魔術師だって
いっぱい いるんだろう？
I'd imagine they could fight without Kanzaki...
神裂がいなくても
戦えそうな気がするけど
That's not the issue.
（土御門）問題なのはそこじゃない
（上条）うん？
It's not about whether they'd actually win or not.
（土御門）
実際に勝てるかどうかではなく
Wars can start simply because one side has the illusion of having a winning chance.
“勝てるかもしれない”と
錯覚させただけで―
戦争ってのは起こっちまうのさ
NO ENTRY
But wait, if this is that serious a problem, shouldn't we ask Index for her help?
（上条）
でも そんなヤバイ問題なら―
インデックスに
協力を仰いだほうがよくないか？
No.
（土御門）
ダメだ　今回の件じゃ
あの禁書目録は使えない
We can't use that forbidden index for this.
We can't let her near any of this, or even let her know about it.
事件の現場に近づけさせることも
事件に関する情報を伝えることも
やっちゃいけないぜ
Why?
（上条）
なんで？
（土御門）
何かが起こるなら
あの子が中心って―
Because if anything were to happen, she'd become the center of attention.
外の魔術師たちのサーチが
集中してるからにゃ
That's how many magicians are looking for her.
もし あの子が動けば―
If she were to be discovered, magicians would come flooding in, aiming for her.
気づいた魔術師たちが
一斉に押し寄せてくるって寸法さ
In other words, we have to do something about it without letting Index notice.
つまり あのインデックスに
魔術のことを気づかせないまま―
なんとかしないと
いけないってわけかよ
ア～ン…
When I rushed back to you after hearing from Yomikawa-sensei,
黄泉川先生からの連絡で
駆けつけたときは―
売れ残った野菜みたいにシナシナで
本当に焦りました
I really panicked since you looked almost like a leftover shriveled vegetable.
プハァ～ッ… ごちそうさまでした
Thanks for the meal!
ハァ… それにしても 当麻は
どこに行っちゃったんだろう
Where did Touma go, though?
It's almost time for lunch!
もうすぐ お昼ご飯だっていうのに
えっ？　あの… ご飯って今…
U-Um... you just had lunch...
Will...
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）私…
（小萌）うん？
Will Touma and I be seperated like this for the rest of the day?
今日は ずっと こんな感じで
当麻とは離れ離れなのかな
I see...
そうですよね
シスターちゃんだって―
You want to enjoy Daihaseisai with Kamijou-chan don't you, Sister?
上条ちゃんと一緒に
大覇星祭を楽しみたいですよね
あっ 大丈夫！
Don't worry!
シスターちゃんにも
参加できるものはあるのです！
There's something you can participate in, Sister!
Yes?
Hey... did you really get lost?
いない… こりゃ マジで迷子か？
Why are you walking around looking like a hero who's about to face the final boss?
さっきから なにをラスボス手前の
勇者さまご一行みたいな―
顔をしているの？
（舞夏）
なんか今にも死にそうな顔してるぞ
You've got an expression on like you're about to die.
おなかが減ってるなら
弁当食ってくか？
Why not go eat something if you're hungry?
Forget that, have you seen Index anywhere?
それより どっかで
インデックスを見なかったか？
I saw the Sister walking over there.
あのシスターなら
あっちを歩いていたけど
Thanks!
（上条）
ありがとうな
It looked like she was being dragged somewhere by that famous little teacher at your school!
なんか上条当麻の学校の
名物ミニ教師に―
手を引っ張られてたぞ
Huh?
うん？　インデックス？
Index?
So it's just you?
お前だけか　インデックスは…
Where's Index?
（小萌）
ごめんなさいです
I'm sorry...
It pains me to make you change here, but...
こんな所で お着替えさせるのは
心苦しいんですけど
Touma!
当麻！　これで何度目か
数えてみるといいかも！
How many times does this make it?!
Uh, well... Index-san?
いや あの… インデックスさん？
Are you okay?
（上条）
大丈夫ですって　事故ですよ 事故
そんなマジにならなくても…
It was an accident!
You don't have to get so serious about it...
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）ンンッ…
（上条）あれ？
Kamijou.
（吹寄）上条
（上条）ハッ…
I came here to look for Tsukiyomi-sensei for some committee work...
運営委員の仕事で 月詠(つくよみ)先生を
捜して やって来てみれば…
And you...
（吹寄）
あんたね… 何やってんのよ
What are you doing?!
You traitor!
この裏切り者が！
Sheesh!
（吹寄）
まったく…
少しは 大会を成功させようという
努力はできないの？　貴様は
Can't you put even a little effort into making this festival a success?
（上条）
今って ウチの学校は
何の競技やってるのかな？
What event is our school in now?
それくらい なんで覚えられない？
You can't even remember that?
そうか
脳の栄養が足りてないようだから
I see. If your brain isn't getting enough nutrients, go get some sugar into your system!
糖分を摂取しなさい
K-Kamijou-san's stupidity won't be cured with that!
そ… そんなことしても―
上条さんのおバカは
直りませんのことよ
Don't you feel bad at all, hearing yourself say that?
自分で言ってて 悲しくないの？
Right now, the second-year girls' tug o' war and the third-year boys' restricted triathlon are on.
２年女子の綱引きと
３年男子選抜のトライアスロン
どっちの応援がいい？
Which event will you go to support?
やっぱり女子か！
そうよね　所詮は上条だものね
The girls, I bet!
But of course, you are Kamijou after all...
とりあえず襟首は もう…
At least don't pull me by my neck...
あっ… それじゃ
Well then.
（上条）あっ…
（吹寄）ほら 早く
Come on already!
ウワッ！
Hey, Kamijou.
ねえ 上条
大覇星祭って つまんない？
Do you find Daihaseisai boring?
You seem restless...
（吹寄）
どうも貴様は浮ついているというか
別のことが気になっているような
感じがする
Like something else is on your mind.
If you're finding today boring, Kamijou, it means I'm not doing enough as a committee member...
上条が
今日 つまんないと感じたのなら
運営委員として
準備を進めてきた私が―
何か
不足していたというわけだからさ
別に
つまんねえなんて思ってねえって
It's not that I think it's boring...
I guess, as someone who worked so hard to come up with all this stuff,
やっぱり 企画を立てて
今日まで頑張ってきた身としては
I kind of want everyone to share fond memories of the event.
みんなに楽しい思い出を
共有してもらいたいと―
思ってしまうのね
わがままかもしれないけどさ
Maybe I'm just being selfish, though.
You really do have something bothering you, don't you?
やはり ほかのことが気になって
しかたないみたいね
No, that's not it—
いや 違うって…
（ぶつかる音）
（上条）ウワッ！
（学生）ごめんなさい！
I'm sorry!
Get away from me, Kamijou Touma!
離れなさい 上条当麻！
（ｵﾘｱﾅ）あ～ん！
（上条）うん？
ウワッ！
I'm sorry!
（ｵﾘｱﾅ）
ごめんね　こんな人混みは
あんまり慣れてなくて
I'm not used to such crowded areas...
It's fine...
いえ
（ｵﾘｱﾅ）
大丈夫？　痛いとこない？
Are you okay?
Are you hurt anywhere?
Your forehead is swelling up.
おでこが赤くなってる
いえ…
It's nothing...
As an apology for bumping into you...
ぶつかってしまった おわびに
ねっ？
Would you like a kiss?
キスのほうがいい？
Yes! A kiss would be—
はい！　キスのほうが…
（殴る音）
（上条）いてて…
Ow...
Well, then.
では…
I need to get back to work.
そろそろ お仕事に戻らなくっちゃ
じゃあね
Bye now.
Hello? Oriana Thompson here.
こちらはオリアナ＝トムソン
聞こえてる？
Can you hear me?
（ﾘﾄﾞｳﾞｨｱ）
本名は慎みなさい
Don't say your real name out loud.
あなたの肉声そのものは
周囲に聞こえているのでしょう？
Is your voice audible to anyone around you?
Nevermind that; I've run into some trouble.
それより ちょっとトラブルがね
It looks like the spell Onee-san cast on me was dispelled.
おねえさんが使っていた あの術式
破られちゃったみたいなの
（ﾘﾄﾞｳﾞｨｱ）原因は？
（ｵﾘｱﾅ）分からないわ
How?
I don't know.
But it's turning me on for some reason.
でも なんか興奮しちゃう
Don't say such obscene things.
（ﾘﾄﾞｳﾞｨｱ）
卑猥(ひわい)な表現は慎むように
Countermeasures?
対応策は？
Let's see...
そうね　まずは 後ろにいる坊やを
まかないといけないわね
First, I'll have to lose that boy behind me.
～♪
Next Episode
（上条）
逃げ回るオリアナに
翻弄される俺たち
Oriana runs around, toying with us.
Stiyl risks his life to investigate the spell she cast.
彼女が仕掛けた術式を
ステイルが命懸けで探索する
そして 見つけた その場所は…
And the place we found...
Next time: "Route Disturb."
次回 「追跡封じ(ルートディスターブ)」
When science and magic cross paths, this epic will begin!
科学と魔術が交差するとき
物語は始まる